{
  "title": "Comparison with as as",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Teenage girls smoke almost ........ boys in many of the villages in West Java. ",
      "answers": ["as good as", "as long as", "as soon as", "as much as"],
      "correct": "as much as"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "I told my son that I would take me to the circus next week ........ he keeps his promise not to fight with his sister. ",
      "answers": ["as good as", "as long as", "as soon as", "as much as"],
      "correct": "as long as"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "You need to go to the hospital ........ possible. An erratic heartbeat can be very dangerous. ",
      "answers": ["as good as", "as long as", "as soon as", "as much as"],
      "correct": "as soon as"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Oh no! I failed all my exams last week. I'm ........ dead when my parents see my final report card.",
      "answers": ["as good as", "as long as", "as soon as", "as much as"],
      "correct": "as good as"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "I bet you don't love me ........ I love you. That would be impossible! ",
      "answers": ["as good as", "as long as", "as soon as", "as much as"],
      "correct": "as much as"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "I will accept your marriage proposal ........ you promise to love me and take care of me forever. ",
      "answers": ["as good as", "as long as", "as soon as", "as much as"],
      "correct": "as long as"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Rampant corruption in Indonesia will continue to happen ........ the government continues to deny that the problem exists. ",
      "answers": ["as good as", "as long as", "as soon as", "as much as"],
      "correct": "as long as"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Many British housewives cannot understand why many British men love watching football twice ........ their women. ",
      "answers": ["as long as", "as soon as", "as good as", "as much as"],
      "correct": "as much as"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Many anti-war protesters think that the President of the United States should withdraw his troops from Iraq....... possible.",
      "answers": ["as long as", "as soon as", "as good as", "as much as"],
      "correct": "as soon as"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "A wise man once said that a change is almost ........ a holiday. ",
      "answers": ["as good as", "as long as", "as soon as", "as much as"],
      "correct": "as good as"
    }
  ]
}
